We thank you Lord for the beautiful city of Miami that we ask for your wisdom and guidance for those who are elected to help us make choices and decisions.
Thank you for those who serve this community, Father, all those jobs and roles that they fulfill.
And we praise you now for this moment. Christ Jesus precious and holy new great.
Amen.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America and to the Republic for which it stands one nation under God, indivisible with liberty and justice for all.
Thank you.
So for public input, let's get a personal pair.
5 A claim list.
Motion is approved.
5B minutes from the November 18, 2025 regular needing most to approve.
5C reject the base bid and bid alternate number one received from goings
Enterprises for the water treatment plant improvements project due to the amount of the bid being larger than the funds available for the project as recommended by
2,582,320 and the bid alternate number one in the amount of $75,000 by goings enterprises were located in the job fund. For a final bid total of 2,657,320 is due for it being above our water funds.
The engineers estimate was $1,700,000 and they came in at $957,300 to help with that. And we're going to take it back out to bid if we can get all this stuff to care.
And this is for the water treatment plant improvement project. I don't see it here, but was there any other bids or was there the other one?
So what's our plan if we reject this for the improvements? We're going to try to get more bidders obviously, you know, just so we get a wider range to see if the prices are really up that much.
I can make a motion to go to the recommendation and reject the base bid and bid alternate.
I'll sign it.
Parker.
Hi.
Jones.
Great.
So the new business, if any, which rhythms is posting this agenda.
Some trustee community now.
Eight trust manager communication.
No, sir.
Nine and during the motion.
Second.
Okay.
Bye.